早晨又来到
Morning's here
The morning's here
阳光照大地
Sunshine is here
晴空万里清
The sky is clear
早晨又来到
The morning's here
你一定要唱吗  今天是星期六
Do you have to do that? It's Saturday!
别这样嘛
Oh, come on!
早晨又来到
Morning's here!
早晨又来到  早晨又来到  阳光照大地
Morning's here! The morning is here! Sunshine's here.
我恨这间公寓
I hate this apartment!
我恨墙壁的颜色
I hate the color of these walls!
我恨这里还是有鸡鸭的味道
I hate the fact that this place still smells like bird!
我恨那个唱歌的人
I hate that singing guy!
不会吧  我好喜欢他
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
早上好  早晨又来到
Morning's here! Morning is here...
闭嘴
Stop it!
小心我宰了你
I will kill you.
我恨我的房间那么小
I hate the fact that my room is so small.
我就觉得空间够用  学学我吧
Hey, I have all the space I need. Do what I did.
莫妮卡  你连床都没有
Monica, you don't even have a bed.
就睡在地上的球里
You sleep in a ball on the floor!
你别再碎碎念了
You know what, I am tired of your bellyaching, okay?
我很努力的把这里收拾得干净舒适
I worked really hard to make this a nice place for us yo live.
我知道  对不起
I know. I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry, okay?
看吧  这真是的好地方
See, this is a great apartment!
闭嘴  这里烂死了
Shut up! This place is a hole!
我还是不敢相信你穿了耳洞
Bite me. I still can't believe you've got an earring!
我知道  我是谁  大卫·鲍伊
I know, I know. Who am I? David Bowie?
他会那样吗
He does that?
不知道  管他呢
I don't know. Whatever.
你这样看起来好邪恶
I think it makes you look really dangerous.
我知道
Oh, I know.
你知道吗
You know what?
要不是为你  我永远不会穿耳洞
I never would've gotten this if it weren't for you.
真的  跟你在一起时
Really. When I'm with you, I'm like
我就变了另一个人  我爱那个人
this whole other guy. I love that guy!
我是说  我也很爱你
I mean, I love you too. A lot.
不过那个人
But that guy!
我爱死他了
I love that guy!
我爱你们两个
I love both of you.
我真不想走
I wish I didn't have to go.
那就别走
Then don't.
留下来  别急着回伦敦
Stay here. Just don't go so soon to London.
再留1天就好
Just one more day.
罗斯  别再引诱我了
Ross, please don't do this to me again.
我真的想留下来
You know I'd stay in a minute,
但我请了那么多假  会被开除的
but I've already missed so much work. They'll fire me.
那你就可以尽情留下来了
So? Then you could stay as long as you want.
我也很想
I wish I could.
不要  不要打包
Oh, no. Don't start packing.
拜托啦
Come on!
你没有领会打包的奥义
I don't think you understand packing.
我不想拖到最后再打包
I just don't want to leave it till last.
上次就是这样把衬裤落下的
Last time I packed in such a rush, I left my knickers here.
我知道  我有偷穿
Yeah, I know. I tried them on.
不会吧
You didn't!
骗你的  我不想学另一个我
No, I didn't. I didn't want to be "that guy."
嚯  嚯  嚯[圣诞老人的笑声]
Ho, ho, ho!
什么
Excuse me?
你的裤子
Your pants.
哦  对  你喜欢吗
Oh yeah! You like them?
我去二手服装店
I went to a used-clothes store
买了一堆孕妇装
and got like a bunch of maternity stuff.
这条裤子好舒服
These are so comfortable.
菲比  那是圣诞裤
Pheobs, those are Santa pants.
什么  圣诞裤
Santa pants.
圣诞老人的裤子
Santa Claus' pants.
才不是  这是孕妇裤
No. They're maternity pants.
你看  还附赠宝宝姓名表
They even came with a list of baby names. See?
这些名字好  这些名字不好
These names are good, and these are bad.
菲比
Hey, Phoebes.
矮人们都好吗
So, how are the elves?
我不知道  那什么...都好吗
I don't know. How are the... you know?
真可恨没法拿你们的衣服开玩笑
Your clothes aren't funny.
我该穿什么去看尼克斯队的比赛
Hey, guys what should I wear to a Knicks game?
上面印有"我是伪球迷"的T恤
A T-shirt that says, "I Don't Belong Here"?
你们有票
You have Knicks tickets?
我妈离婚时分到我爸的季票
My Mom got my Dad's season tickets in the divorce,
就送给我了
so she gave them to me.
看上去位置很好
Apparently, they're pretty good seats.
天呐  几乎就在场边
Oh, my God! Those are almost on the floor!
你们想要吗
Do you guys want these?
那当然了
Yeah, we do!
那就给你们
Well, you got them!
只要把这里还给我们
Just give us our apartment back.
我可没料到这一出
Oh, I didn't see that coming.
你们是说真的
Are you serious?
得了  我们知道你们有多爱这些票
Come on. We know what these are worth.
你们以为我们是白痴吗
What, you think we're stupid?
不是白痴  是很过分
Not stupid. You're meaner than I thought.
如何
What do you say?
想都别想
Forget it, okay?
我才不会为球票放弃我的单身公寓
I'm not giving up my bachelor pad for some basketball seats.
你的单身公寓
Your "bachelor pad"?
你带女生回来过吗
Have you even had a girl up here?
没有
No.
但是乔伊有  我早上都会跟她们聊天
But Joey has, and I usually talk to them in the morning time.
没错
Yeah, you do!
拜托啦
Come on!
甘瑟  请给我两杯卡布奇诺
Gunther, can I get two cups of chino, please?
真好笑
Good one.
拜托  季票耶
Come on. Season tickets!
季票耶  你知道那意味着什么吗
Season tickets! You know what that means?
别想了  我绝不让出那层公寓
Forget it! I'm not giving up the apartment.
小时候  我爸的单位都会送季票
When I was a kid, my dad's company gave season tickets
给业绩第一的业务员
to the No. 1 salesman every year.
我爸从来没拿到过
My dad never won.
当然  他不在销售部
Of course, he wasn't in sales division.
但我还是一直耿耿于怀
But still, I never ever ever forgot that!
你们好
Hey guys!
天呐
Oh, my God!
我们笑你笑得还不够吗
We don't make enough fun of you already?
艾蜜莉说服我去打耳洞的
Oh, yeah. Emily convinced me to do it.
你知道威猛乐队解散了吧
You do know that Wham broke up?
我喜欢  关键是艾蜜莉喜欢
I like it. Emily likes it. That's what counts.
你们好吗
So, how are you guys doing?
别戴了耳环还装正经
Don't try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.
艾蜜莉呢
Where's Emily?
去跟她舅舅道别
She's saying goodbye to her uncle.
-她不是才刚来  -对啊
- Didn't she, like, just get here?  - Yeah!
别激动  大哥
Easy, tiger.
我好讨厌这样
I just, I hate this so much.
每次去机场接她  我都好开心
Every time I go pick her up at the airport, it's so great.
但是我又会想
But at the same time I'm thinking,
过两天又要送她来机场了
"I'll be right back there in a couple of days, dropping her off."
-那你要怎么办  -没办法
- So what are you gonna do?  - Nothing. There's nothing to do.
她住在那里  我住在这里
She lives there. I live here.
她得搬来这里
She'd have to move here.
她应该搬来这里
She should move here.
什么
What?
-我可以叫她跟我住  -你说真的吗
- I can ask her to live with me.  - Are you serious?
为什么不行
Why not? I mean, why not?
你才认识她6星期
You've only known her six weeks!
我冰箱里有盒牛奶
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge
都不止放了六星期
I've had a longer relationship with.
我跟她在一起时  就好像...
Look, guys, when I'm with her, it's like...
她会激发出我好的一面
She brings out this great side of me.
我爱她  知道吗
I mean, I love her, you know?
我也爱那盒牛奶
And I love the milk!
但我不会要一个英国女孩跟我同居
But I won't ask some British girl to move in with me.
乔伊  该你说了
Joey, you say things now.
罗斯  他说得对  艾蜜莉很好
Look, Ross. He's right. Emily's great.
她很棒
She's great!
但这样太快了  你只会吓到她
But this is way too soon. You're only gonna scare her.
我不想吓到她
I don't want to do that.
没错  别坏了好事  别太心急
You don't want to wreck it. Don't go too fast.
你们说得对  我明白了
No. You're right. I know, you're right.
我不会这样
I'm not going to do it.
-谢了  两位  -客气
- Thanks guys. - No problem.
摇滚时一定要叫醒我
Just remember to wake us up before you go-go.
这太难了  太难了
It's too hard. Too hard!
两位  赢得季票的最后机会
All right boys. Last chance for the tickets.
否则我就送给我的新男友约书亚
Otherwise, I give them to my new boyfriend, Joshua.
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
等一下  拜托  跟她们换啦
Wait, wait. Come on, come on! Let's trade.
时机正好  我刚把马桶堵住
The timing's perfect! I just clogged the toilet!
我跟你一样想要球票
I want those basketball seats as much as you do.
但是住过了大房决不能搬回去
But we can't live in the smaller apartment after living here!
你没看过《献给阿尔杰农的花》吗
Didn't you ever read Flowers for Algernon?
看过
Yes.
你没看过《运动画报》吗
Didn't you ever read Sports Illustrated?
没  我没偷看你的
No, I didn't read yours!
我们晚上就可以去看球
Come on. We can go to the game tonight!
听着  想让我考虑换
Look, the only way I'll consider this is
除非她们提出比季票更好的东西
if they offer a lot more than just season seats.
-是尼克斯队耶!  -去他的尼克斯克队
- It's the Knicks! - Screw the Knicks!
我不是那个意思  我是说
I didn't mean that. I just meant that
这间公寓的价值要更大
the apartment is won'th so much more.
尼克斯队万岁
And the Knicks rule all.
对  尼克斯队万岁
Yeah, the Knicks rule all!
怎样  要不要
So? Are you going to do it?
不要
No, we're not going to do that.
因为这个交易不公平
You know why? Because it's not an even trade.
好  听着
All right, okay, look.
要是你们能保住公寓又拿到球票呢
What if you could keep the apartment and the tickets?
成交
Done!
让我说完  我是说我们来赌
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet.
赢的人通杀
Winner takes all.
我们可能输光光
We could end up with nothing.
或是通杀
Or you could end up with everything.
我喜欢
I like that.
-怎么样?  -不
- What do you say?  -No.
赌吧
Just do it!
真有说服力啊
Oh! I'm convinced!
拜托啦  我也会为你这么做
Come on, man! You know I'd do it for you.
因为你是我最好的朋友
Because you're my best friend.
好吧  但你1整年不准再用这招
All right. But you can't use that again for a whole year.
我赌了
I'm in.
好激动人心  你们要赌什么
This is so exciting! What are you going to bet?
我们就让菲比决定
I think we should let Phoebe decide
因为只有她没有利害关系
because she's the only one who's impartial,
而且她好美
and she's so pretty.
我想到一个游戏
I have a game!
-很棒喔  -是什么游戏
- This is great! - What's the game? What's the game?
没有名字  就叫菲比球吧
It doesn't have a name. No, okay. Phoebe Ball!
不  没有名字
No, it doesn't have a name.
莫妮卡
Okay, Monica.
你最喜欢树的哪一点
What is your favorite thing about trees?
-树是绿色的  -很好  加5分
- They're green? - Good! Five points!
乔伊  同样的问题
Joey. Same question.
-树很高  -3分
- They're tall. - Three points!
都答得很好  但标准答案是叶子多
Both fine answers, but we were looking for leafy. Leafy.
这游戏说不通
That's not even a game.
闭嘴  我们领先
Shut up. We're winning!
你们想速战速决吗
You want to finish this right now?
我们抽牌  点数大的赢
We get a deck of cards. High card wins.
如何
What do you say?
-好  就这么办  -我有牌
- Let's do it! - Oh, I have cards!
在这里
Yeah. Here.
这是魔术牌
No, these are the trick deck.
这一副
Here, yes.
好  你们先抽
Okay, you guys pick first.
-4点  -小点数
- Four. - That's a low one!
菲比  你看  我不敢看
Phoebe, you look. I can't do it.
为什么我就敢看
What makes you think I can?
老A
Ace!
你们在高兴什么
Why are you screaming and hugging?
我们把这套公寓赢回来了
We won our apartment back!
什么  老A最大  JQKA
What? Ace is high! Jack, queen, king, ace!
不对  1点最小  A234
No! Ace is low! Ace, two, three, four!
我不知道
I don't know.
你们看
Look it!
再抽一次
Come on, pick again!
我要公寓  我要公寓
Come on, apartment! Come on, apartment!
Q点数大
I know queen is high!
但是大不过...
Not as high as...
成功了  老K
It worked! King!
再抽一次  再抽一次
We pick again! We pick again!
-为什么  -我不知道
- Why?  - I don't know.
球票请拿来
Tickets, please.
场边区哟
Courtside, baby!
说真的  承让  承让
Seriously, good game, though. Good game.
她们气什么气  公寓都还给她们了
What are they so mad about? They got the apartment back.
没还她们
No, they didn't.
趁你不在打包好了
Packed while you were gone.
我留了几条衬裤在枕头底下
I left knickers under your pillow.
搬来跟我住好吗
Move in with me?
什么
What?
别被吓到
Don't be scared.
我知道听起来很疯狂  别人会说太快了
I know it sounds crazy, and people will say it's too soon,
但是你想想  那样多棒啊
but just think. Think how great it would be.
我不知道
I don't know.
要我离开伦敦...
Leaving London...
我的家人都在那里...
My whole family lives there...
-我的工作  -你可以在这里找工作
- My job. - You'll get a job here.
我常听说外国人到来
I always hear about the foreigners coming in
把美国人的工作都抢走了
and stealing American jobs.
你也可以
That could be you.
但事关我的人生
Yeah, but it's my whole life.
你来英国
You come to England.
我不行  我很愿意  但我儿子在这里
No, I can't. I would. I really would. But my son is here.
我不能离开他  没别的办法了吗
I can't leave him. You don't think there's any way?
我看是没有了
I don't think so.
如果是长久的打算就不同了
It would be different if it was way into the future
例如结婚什么的
and we were getting married.
什么
What?
好  我不该提结婚的
Right. I shouldn't have said "married."
别被我吓到
Please don't go freaky on me.
我不是认真的  我收回
I didn't mean it. I didn't say it. I take it back.
不  不要收回
No. Don't.
何不就这么做
Why don't we?
做什么
Why don't we what?
结婚啊
Get married.
你疯了
You are mad!
我没有  这样很完美
No, I'm not! It's perfect.
比你搬来住更棒
It's better than you moving here.
我们可以永远在一起  这才是我想要的
It's us together forever, and that's what I want.
-我们才认识6星期  -我知道
- We've known each other 6 weeks!  - I know.
那又怎样  谁说不行  这样就不行吗
So what? Who's to say?  Does that mean we can't do it?
听着  我跟卡罗尔在一起4年才结婚
Look. I was with Carol for four years before we got married...
结果我跟一个怀孕的拉拉离婚
...and I wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian.
这么做...
I mean, this...
对我们是顺理成章
This makes sense for us.
我们第一次约会就跑去佛蒙特度周末
Our first date, we ended up spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
昨晚我还去穿耳洞  我
I mean, last night I got my ear pierced. Me!
我们在一起感觉很对
This feels right.
不是吗
Doesn't it?
我爸妈会气死
My parents will be really mad.
你答应了吗   那是同意吗
Are you saying, "Yes"? Is that "Yes"?
是的
Yes.
-我们要结婚了  -天哪
- We're getting married!  - Oh, my God!
我们要结婚了
We're getting married!
过来
Come here, come here.
-艾蜜莉  你愿意嫁给我吗  -愿意
- Emily, will you marry me?  - Yes.
有一点小
It's a bit small.
真是的  我还以为这样会很浪漫
Damn! I thought that'd be romantic as hell.
是很浪漫
It was.
真是史上最棒的位子
Those were, like, the best seats ever!
要不要把衣服送给她们表示和解
Should we give these to the girls? Like a peace offering?
好主意  反正不要钱又太小
That's very nice. Plus, they were free and too small.
天哪
Oh, God!
你要喝酒吗
Hey, you want a beer?
我的天
I know!
开门  开门  开门
Open up! Open up! Open up!
明天早上再说
We'll discuss it in the morning.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我们把公寓抢回来了
We took our apartment back!
不关我的事
I had nothing to do with it.
好吧  是我的主意  但我并不开心
Okay, it was my idea. But I don't feel good about it.
我们现在就换回来
We are switching back right now.
不要  我们不走
No, we're not. We're not leaving!
你们总得出门  你们都有工作
You're gonna have to leave sometime. You both have jobs.
等你们去上班  我们就换回来
As soon as you do, we'll switch back!
你们阻止不了的
There's nothing you can do to stop us.
-对吧  乔伊  -我不知道
- Right, Joe? - I don't know.
什么
What?
我不想再搬了
I don't want to move again, with...
我不管  这是我们的公寓被她们偷了...
This is our apartment and they stole...
你们偷了
You stole!
我们的公寓  我们光明正大地赢了两次
Our apartment! We won it fair and square. Twice!
我现在就要换回来
And I am getting it back right now!
I'm getting it back right now!
好
All right.
我们料到你会有这种反应
We figured you might respond this way,
所以我们有预备方案
so we have a backup offer.
不要  不接受任何妥协
No more offers. You can't offer anything to us!
-让我们留在这里  -为了表示感谢
- Let us keep the apartment and... - As a thank you
瑞秋和我会接吻1分钟
Rachel and I will kiss for 1 minute.
-完全值得  -好爽的1分钟
- Totally won'th it! - That was one good minute!
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night.  -Good night.
-男人真是白痴  -就是啊
- Men are such idiots.  - I know.
用一件这么小儿科的事
Can you believe something that stupid
就把家换回来了
actually got us our apartment back?
真好笑
It's so funny to think
要是你们上次比完就这么做
if you had just done that after the last contest
谁都不用搬家
no one would have had to move at all.
就装做没这回事
Let's pretend that's not true.
围巾织好了
Scarf's done.
快点
Come on, come on!
怎么了
What's going on?
罗斯有大事要宣布
Ross has some big thing to tell everyone.
艾蜜莉和我决定...
Emily and I, we decided...
结婚
to get married.
什么
What?
你也怀孕了吗
Oh, are you pregnant too?
没有
No.
什么...怎么...
When did... How did you...
我们就是决定要结婚
We just decided to go for it.
这个决定是仓促了些
We know it's a bit hasty...
但是...感觉真的很好
but it just feels so right.
我正在告诉他们...
I was just telling the guys...
我听到了
Yeah, I heard.
这很棒
I think it's great!
我真替你高兴
I'm so happy for you!
是啊  恭喜
Well, yeah! Congratulations!
真不敢相信你居然要结婚了
I can't believe you're getting married!
莫妮卡和瑞秋激吻了
Monica and Rachel made out.
早晨又来到
Morning's here
The morning's here
阳光照大地
Sunshine is here
晴空万里清
The sky is clear
早晨又来到
The morning's here
-你回来了  -准备就绪
- Hey, you're back! - Hey, get into gear
早餐就快上桌
Breakfast is near
夜晚的黑暗一扫而空
The dark of night has disappeared
-我们明天见  -明天见
- I'll see you tomorrow morning! - Okay!